const level6Questions = [
 {
        question: "Tiếng Trung",
        answers: ["文 (wén)", "中文 (Zhōngwén)"],
        correct: "中文 (Zhōngwén)",
    },
    {
        question: "Tiếng Ả Rập",
        answers: ["阿拉伯文 (Ālābó wén)", "德文 (Dé wén)"],
        correct: "阿拉伯文 (Ālābó wén)",
    },
    {
        question: "Tiếng Nga",
        answers: ["俄文 (É wén)", "法文 (Fǎ wén)"],
        correct: "俄文 (É wén)",
    },
    {
        question: "Tiếng Nhật",
        answers: ["韩文 (Hán wén)", "日文 (Rì wén)"],
        correct: "日文 (Rì wén)",
    },
    {
        question: "Tiếng Tây Ban Nha",
        answers: ["西班牙文 (Xībānyá wén)", "英文 (Yīng wén)"],
        correct: "西班牙文 (Xībānyá wén)",
    },
    {
        question: "Mike",
        answers: ["朋友 (péngyǒu)", "麦克 (Màikè)"],
        correct: "麦克 (Màikè)",
    },
    {
        question: "Trương Đông",
        answers: ["张东 (Zhāng Dōng)", "麦克 (Màikè)"],
        correct: "张东 (Zhāng Dōng)",
    },
    {
        question: "Giáo sư",
        answers: ["教授 (jiàoshòu)", "校长 (xiàozhǎng)"],
        correct: "教授 (jiàoshòu)",
    },
    {
        question: "Buổi trưa",
        answers: ["中午 (zhōngwǔ)", "吃 (chī)"],
        correct: "中午 (zhōngwǔ)",
    },
    {
        question: "Ăn",
        answers: ["吃 (chī)", "饭 (fàn)"],
        correct: "吃 (chī)",
    },
    {
        question: "Nhà ăn, căn tin",
        answers: ["食堂 (shítáng)", "馒头 (mántou)"],
        correct: "食堂 (shítáng)",
    },
    {
        question: "Bánh bao chay",
        answers: ["馒头 (mántou)", "米饭 (mǐfàn)"],
        correct: "馒头 (mántou)",
    },
    {
        question: "Gạo",
        answers: ["米 (mǐ)", "米饭 (mǐfàn)"],
        correct: "米 (mǐ)",
    },
    {
        question: "Cần, muốn",
        answers: ["要 (yào)", "个 (gè)"],
        correct: "要 (yào)",
    },
    {
        question: "Bát, chén",
        answers: ["碗 (wǎn)", "鸡蛋 (jīdàn)"],
        correct: "碗 (wǎn)",
    },
    {
        question: "Trứng gà",
        answers: ["鸡蛋 (jīdàn)", "鸡 (jī)"],
        correct: "鸡蛋 (jīdàn)",
    },
];

export default level6Questions;
